(Sheldon:)Well, now, don't get defensive.
(Sheldon:)You're oddly-shaped,
but you got the girl.
(Dr Lorvis:)So, I've noticed Leonard
gets teased a lot
(Dr Lorvis:)about his relationship
with Penny.
(Sheldon:)Yes. If you'd like to join in,
(Sheldon:)the premise is their love seems
unlikely and doomed to failure.
(Dr Lorvis:)So, you think
she'll be single soon?
(Sheldon:)Oh, if you want
to get in on the pool,
(Sheldon:)you're too late...
(Sheldon:)All the squares
have been purchased.
(Bermadette:)Interesting.
(Dr Lorvis:)Excuse me, I have to
take care of something.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, as your friend I feel
(Sheldon:)I should tell you something.
What?
(Sheldon:)I'm still upset
about that peanut sauce.
(Dr Lorvis:)Oh, could you
hold the door?
(Amy:)Nice flowers.
Thank you.
(Dr Lorvis:)They're for a girl.